嗨
Hi!
- 嗨   - 嗨 欢迎你回来
- Hey!    - Hey! Welcome back!
- 蜜月旅行如何？ - 非常美好
- How was the honeymoon?    - Oh, incredible!
香槟 烛光晚餐 月光下沙滩散步
Oh, champagne, candle-lit dinners, moonlight walks on the beach.
- 真是浪漫   - 哦
- It was so romantic.    - Oh.
- 麦克呢？ - 他去看医生了
- So where's Mike?   - Oh, he's at the doctor.
我们在那里时 他完全没大便
He didn't poop while we were there.
- 真高兴你回来了 我需要你帮忙   - 怎么了？
- I'm glad you're back. I need your help.    - Oh, why, what's up?
我有一场试演 而我得说法语
I have an audition for this play, and I have to speak French...
我的履历表上写着 "法语流利"
...which, according to my résumé, I'm fluent in.
- 乔伊 你不该在履历上作假   - 是啊 你不该这么做
- Joey, you shouldn't lie on your résumé.    - Yeah, you really shouldn't.
顺便一提 你在开罗挖掘了 整整一年 还可以吗？
By the way, how was that yearlong dig in Cairo?
还可以
It was okay.
我不知道你会说法语
I did not know you spoke French.
你真性感
Oh, oh, you're so sexy.
- 你会帮我吗？ - 当然
- Well, so will you help me?     - Sure.
说真的 别说了 我会扑到你身上
Ha, ha, seriously, stop it. I'm gonna jump on you.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.    - Hi.
你干嘛穿我的围裙？
Why are you wearing my apron?
我在为艾瑞卡做饼干
I'm making cookies for Erica.
我们差不多得走了 她的飞机约一小时后抵达
We have to leave soon. Her plane comes in in about an hour.
她来的时候 可以介绍你们 为我太太…
When she gets here, is it okay if I introduce you two as my wife...
以及怀着我小孩的女人吗？
...and the woman who's carrying my child, ha, ha?
不行吗？
No?
离婚呢？
Divorce?
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.    - Hey.
- 你们知道瑞秋在哪儿吗？ - 早都没见过她
- Uh, you know where Rachel is?     - Haven't seen her since morning.
真不敢相信 她半个小时前 就该带着艾玛和我碰面的
It's unbelievable. She was supposed to meet me a half-hour ago with Emma.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey!     - Hey!
- 这是给艾瑞卡的   - 她能吃完所有的饼干吗？
- These are for Erica!     - She's gonna eat all those cookies?
我希望生出白白胖胖的宝宝
Well, I want the baby to come out all cute and fat!
- 为什么艾瑞卡要来？ - 我们想多了解她
- So, uh, why is Erica coming to visit?     - We wanna get to know her better.
她从来没有来过纽约 所以她想去观光景点看看
And, uh, she's never been to New York, so she wants to see the tourist spots:
自由女神像 帝国大厦
Statue of Liberty, Empire State Building.
那里总是有很多人 就像是被赶入围栏的牛只
Oh, there's always so many people, and they're being corralled like cattle.
总是有个白痴会嗥嗥叫
And, you know, there's always some idiot who goes, "Moo."
如果你觉得很蠢的话 那你干嘛学？
Well, if it annoys you so much, then why do you do it?
嗨 嗨
ROSS: Oh, hi! Hi!
- 谢谢你们晚了三十分钟才出现   - 罗斯
- Thanks for showing up 30 minutes late.     - Ross.
我敢保证你有绝佳的借口 到美容院做头发？
No, I'm sure you have a great excuse. What was it, a hair appointment?
指甲沙龙？还是巴尼百货公司有打折？
Uh, a mani-pedi? Was there a sale at Barneys?
我父亲心脏病医
My father had a heart attack.
当我在逛巴尼百货公司时
While I was at Barneys.
- 我的天 瑞秋   - 亲爱的？
- Oh, my God, Rach.     - Honey?
- 我很抱歉   - 他还好吗？
- I'm so sorry.     - Uh, is he okay?
他会没事的 但是他现在还没醒
Yeah, he's gonna be fine, but he's heavily sedated.
我和你一起去长岛
Okay, I'm gonna go to Long Island with you.
- 你现在不能自己一个人   - 不用 我没问题的
- I mean, you can't be alone right now.     - No, come on, I'm totally okay.
我不需要你和我去
I don't need you to come.
- 我自己可以处理的   - 但为了我 还是让我一起去
- I can totally handle this on my own.     - Still, still, let me come for me.
好吧 如果你非去不可的话
Okay. If you really need to.
我打赌有人会想要来片 摩妮卡的现烤饼干
I bet someone could use one of Monica's freshly baked cookies.
- 正合我意   - 哦
- Oh, I really could.    - Oh.
哦
Oh.
(中央咖啡厅)
看起来蛮简单的
All right, it seems pretty simple.
你的第一句台词是"我叫克劳德"
Your first line is, "My name is Claude."
- 嗯   - 所以跟着我念
- Okay.     - So just repeat after me.
- 我们再念一次   - 好的
- Well, let's try it again.    - Okay.
这不太像…
Huh. It's not...
我刚刚说的
...quite what I'm saying.
是吗？我听起来却一模一样
Really? Sounds exactly the same to me.
- 是吗？ - 没错
- It does, really?    - Yeah.
- 我们再试一次   - 好的
- Let's just try it again.    - Okay.
- 仔细听   - 没问题
- Really listen.    - Got it.
好
Okay.
大家好
Hey, you guys!
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.    - Hey!
我要和你们介绍一位很特别的人
I want you to meet someone really special.
- 菲比 这位是艾瑞卡   - 你好
- Phoebe, this is Erica.    - Hi.
- 这是宝宝   - 你好
- And this is the baby!    - Oh, hi.
- 乔伊 艾瑞卡 宝宝   - 你好
- Joey,EHca,baby.    - Hi.
各位 艾瑞卡 宝宝
Everyone, Erica! Baby!
- 摩妮卡 冷静 自制   - 哈哈
- Monica. Calm. Self.    - Ha, ha.
- 坐下吧   - 谢谢
- Hey, sit down.    - Thank you.
很高兴认识你们 不敢相信我在这里
It's really nice to meet you guys. I can't believe I'm here.
欢迎来到纽约市 或者我应该说…
Well, welcome to New York City, or should I say:
纽约市
...New York City.
你为什么要那样说？
Why would you say that?
你们今天打算要做什么？
Okay. What are you gonna be doing today?
我什么都想看看 时代广场 康尼岛 洛克斐勒中心
Well, I wanna see everything! Times Square, Coney Island, Rockefeller Center.
你应该到自由女神像上面看看
You should walk to the top of the Statue of Liberty.
- 好啊 我们去看看   - 太好了
- Oh, yeah, let's do that.    - Great.
宝宝最好是一个很好的宝宝
This baby better be really good.
你好 我是来探望我父亲的 我是瑞秋葛林
Hi, um, uh, excuse me, I'm here to see my father. My name is Rachel Green.
- 我是罗斯盖勒博士   - 罗斯 拜托 这里是医院
- And I'm Dr. Ross Geller.    - Ross, please, this is a hospital.
这里的博士头衔才值得重视
That actually means something here.
- 我们可以进去看他吗？ - 当然
- So can we please go in?    - Absolutely.
瑞秋 我想我在这里等…
Rach, I think I'm gonna wait out here...
因为我的喉咙痒痒的 我不想要传染给他
...because, uh, my throat is feeling a little scratchy. I don't wanna infect him.
- 罗斯 拜托   - 我才不怕他 你不用怕他 我真的不舒服
- Ross, please. Don't be so scared of him.    - I am not scared of him. I'm really sick.
- 他打了镇静剂 没有知觉   - 我觉得好多了
- He's under sedation, so he's out.    - I'm feeling better.
我的天
Oh, my God.
喔 哇
Oh, oh, wow.
我买给他的耳鼻毛修剪器 难道只是浪费钱吗？
That ear and nose hair trimmer I got him was just money down the drain, huh?
葛林小姐 你父亲的医生在线上 你要不要和他说话？
Ms. Green? Your father's doctor's on the phone if you'd like to speak to him.
好的 你待在这儿没事吧？
Oh, great. Um, are you gonna be okay?
- 他没有意识 我们没事的   - 好吧
- He's unconscious. We'll be just fine.    - Okay.
- 电视把你吵醒了吗？ - 不是
- Uh, did the TV wake you?     - No.
你把脚跷在我的床上 拉到我的导尿管
When you put your feet up on my bed, you tugged on my catheter.
脾气好暴
Ouchy.
盖勒 你来这里做什么？
What are you doing here, Geller?
我和瑞秋一起来 她应该很快就回来了
Well, I came with Rachel, who should be back any second.
- 有什么新鲜事吗？ - 我的心脏病有点发作了
- So, what's new?    - Oh, I had a little heart attack.
这样很痛苦吗？
Right. Is it painful?
你指的是心脏病 还是和你讲话？
What, the heart attack or sitting here talking to you?
我们来看看能不能把瑞秋叫回这里
Let's see if we can get that Rachel back in here.
你有什么新鲜事？ 最近有没有让我其他的女儿怀孕？
So, what's new with you? Knocked up any more of my daughters lately?
没有 只有一个 瑞秋
Nope. Just the one. Rachel!
不是
No!
好吧 或许拆开来念会比较好
Okay, maybe if we just break it down.
我们一次念一个音节 好 跟着我念
Okay, let's try it one syllable at a time. Okay, so repeat after me.
太好了 念快一点
Great! Okay, faster.
- 太难了 我教不了你 - 你要做什么？
- Okay, it's too hard. I can't teach you.    - What are you doing?
我得在拿你的头去撞墙前先走一步
I have to go before I put your head through a wall.
别走 我需要你 明天就是试演了
No, no. Don't go, I need you! My audition is tomorrow!
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.    - Hi.
我本来想做晚餐…
I was gonna make us some dinner...
但是你爸爸的冰箱里 只有培根和鲜奶油
...but all I found in your dad's fridge was bacon and heavy cream.
我想我们解开了 他得到心脏病的谜团
I think we solved the mystery of the heart attack.
- 你打电话给你爸妈了吗？ - 打了 艾玛很好
- Did you call your parents?    - Oh, yeah. Emma's doing great.
那就好
Oh, good.
哇哦
Wow.
怎么了？
What?
我不敢相信我在瑞秋葛林的房间里
I just can't believe I'm in Rachel Green's room.
- 你来过我房间的   - 才没有
- You've been in my room before.    - Hah, yeah, sure, right. Ha, ha.
我哪会有机会进来 瑞秋葛林的房间？
Like I'd ever be in Rachel Green's room.
我跟你说 听你叫我全名 感觉非常奇怪
Okay, I gotta tell you, it's really weird when you use my whole name.
- 喔 哈哈   - 抱歉
- Oh, ha, ha.    - Sorry.
- 你没事吧？ - 没事
- You okay?    - Yeah.
- 挺难受的一天   - 是啊
- Yeah, you had a rough day, huh?    - Yeah.
看到他那样很奇怪 你知道吗？因为他是个医生
It's just so weird seeing him like that, you know? I mean, he's a doctor.
人们认为医生是不会生病的
You don't expect doctors to get sick.
但我们也会生病
But we do.
他会没事的 瑞秋
Well, he's gonna be okay, Rach.
啊
Aw.
我不希望他醒来身边没人 我要去医院陪他
I don't want him to wake up alone. I should go to the hospital.
- 什么？不…听着   - 什么？
- What? No, no. Hey, hey, look.    - What?
他们给他吃了许多药
They gave him a lot of medication.
你就算去了 他也不会知道你在那
He wouldn't even know if you were there.
我们明早第一件事就是去看他
We'll go see him first thing in the morning.
- 是吗？我不应该觉得内疚吗？ - 天啊 当然不用
- Really? I shouldn't feel guilty?    - No... God, hey.
瑞秋 你是个很棒的女儿
Rach, you've been an amazing daughter, okay?
- 现在你需要休息一下   - 好吧 或许你说得对
- Right now you need to get some rest.    - Okay, maybe you're right.
晚安
Good night.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
你可不可以在这里陪我一会儿？
Would you stay here with me for a little while?
- 当然   - 真好
- Sure.    - Okay.
- 谢谢你今天陪我去   - 不客气
- Thank you for coming with me today.    - Oh, of course.
瑞秋葛林很高兴你在她的房问
Rachel Green is very happy you're in her room.
- 我也是 过来   - 不
- Me too. Come here.   - No.
我今晚不想一个人
I just don't wanna be alone tonight.
好吧 我可以拿个睡袋来 还是…
Okay, well, um, I can maybe grab a sleeping bag or...
不 瑞秋
No, Rach!
不好意思 我不觉得这是个好主意
I'm sorry, I just don't think this is a good idea.
我们还没做 我们怎么知道？
Well, we won't know that until we do it, will we?
听我说
No, um, uh, look, um.
你因为你父亲的事而感到难过 而且你觉得很脆弱
You are upset about your father, and you're feeling vulnerable...
我觉得这样不好
...and I just don't feel it would be right.
我觉得我在占你便宜
I feel like I'd be, you know, taking advantage of you.
什么？占便宜？我给你便宜 好好享受
What...? Taking advantage? I am giving you the advantage. Enjoy!
我知道一定会很棒的
Look, I'm sure it would be great...
但我们其中一人得头脑清楚
...but I think one of us has to be thinking clearly.
所以我要走了
So I'm gonna go.
哇
Wow.
好吧
Okay.
- 明天早上见   - 嗯
- I'll see you in the morning.    - Mm-hm.
已经有四个月没和人上床 我刚刚的行为应该获颁奖章
I haven't had sex in four months. I should get a medal for that!
谢谢你们带我去那么多地方 我玩得很愉快
Thanks so much for taking me to all those places. I had a great time.
很高兴你很开心 不过因为钱德 我得向你道歉
Oh, I'm glad. Listen, I wanna apologize about Chandler, though.
- 我没有料到会这样   - 纽约实在太棒了
- I just did not see this coming.    - New York is awesome!
- 你是怎么回事？ - 我去过那些地方…
- What is with you?    - I've been to these places before...
但是我没有仔细地看
...but I've never really seen them.
没错 当你嗥嗥叫时 错过了不少
Yeah, you miss a lot when you're mooing.
- 谢谢你们带我到处看看   - 是我们的荣幸
- Thanks so much for showing me around.    - Oh, it was our pleasure.
我们很高兴能更了解你
We're so much enjoying getting to know you.
你们还有没有想知道什么？
Well, if there's anything else you wanna know...
额
Oh, uh...
好的
Okay, um.
我们可以问有关 孩子父亲的问题吗？
Can we ask you some questions about the father?
当然
Oh, sure. Yeah.
他是我高中时的男友 美式足球队长 很可爱
Well, he was my high-school boyfriend, captain of the football team, really cute.
- 他拿奖学金 上过大学   - 很好啊
- Got a scholarship and went to college.    - That's great.
是啊 应该是他没错
Yeah, it's almost definitely him.
什么意思？
How's that, now?
有可能是另一个男的
Well, there's a chance it's another guy.
我只有和两个男的交往过…
I mean, I've only ever been with two guys...
但是同时交往的
...but they sort of overlapped.
那另外一个男友是做什么的？
So, what does the other guy do?
- 他也上过大学吗？ - 不 他在监狱里
- Does he go to college too?    - No, he's in prison.
哦
Oh.
他遭到诬告还是怎么了？
Well, um, was he falsely accused of something?
不是
No.
他用铲子把他爸打死了
He killed his father with a shovel.
除此之外 他是个很好的人
Other than that, he's a great guy.
他爸爸可不这么认为
I'll bet his dad doesn't think so.
- 你醒着吗？ - 我当然醒着
- Are you awake?    - Of course I'm awake.
我想从现在开始 我都得保持清醒
Assume from now on that I'm always awake.
我们不知道他是不是孩子的爸 可能是美式足球队长
All right, we don't know that it's him. I mean, it could be the football guy.
亲爱的 我们的运气很糟 当然会是铲子杀手
Honey, it's us. Of course it's the shovel killer.
好吧 如果真的是他
Well, all right, let's say that it is him.
我们会不想要小孩吗？当然不会
Would we not want the baby? No.
- 我们对待小孩会有不同吗？ - 我会盯着他
- Would we treat him any differently?    - I'd keep an eye on him.
我们必须查出爸爸是谁
We have to find out which the father is.
- 怎么查？ - 我不知道
- How?    - I don't know.
- 应该有测试可以查出来吧？ - 是啊 或许我们只是过度反应
- They have tests for these things, right?    - Yeah, but maybe we're overreacting.
你说得倒轻松 他是杀父凶手
Easy for you to say. He's a father killer.
他大概很爱他的妈咪
He probably loves his mommy.
搞不好他那用铲子的手臂上 有刺"妈"这个字
He's probably got a tattoo that says "Mom" on his shovel-wielding arm.
让我们从一数到五
We'll now count from one to five.
- 很好   - 谢谢你
- Good job.    - Thank you.
- 嘿   - 嘿 乔伊
- Hey.    - Hey, JOEY
我很抱歉 昨天就那样走掉 我想了好久
Listen, I feel really badly about yesterday, and I thought about it a lot.
我太没耐心了 我们再来试试
No, I was too impatient. So let's try it again.
没关系 我不需要你教我了
That's okay. I don't need your help.
我自己抓到诀窍了 而且我还说得挺好的
I worked on it myself, and I gotta say, I am pretty good.
- 是吗？我可以听听看吗？ - 当然…
- Really, can I hear some of it?    - Sure, sure.
好的
Okay. Ahem.
你看
See?
你不是…
Right, but you're not...
You're not... You're...
我再说一次 你说的不是法语
Again, you're not speaking French!
我是在说法语 而且我会得到那个演出机会
Oh, well, I think I am! Yeah, and I think I'm definitely gonna get the part!
你为什么会那么笃定？
How could you possibly think that?
录音带上的人说我念得很好
The guy on the tape said I was doing a good job!
瑞秋 可以帮我倒杯咖啡吗？
Hey, Rach, can you grab me a cup of coffee?
当然
Sure.
整个早上你都很安静 没事吧？
You've been quiet all morning. ls everything okay?
嗯
Mm-hm.
- 你确定你没事？ - 是的
- You sure you're all right?    - Yep.
好吧
Okay. Um.
我要去买些早餐
Well, I'm gonna go, uh, grab us some breakfast.
- 顺便提一下   - 我就知道
- FYI.    - There it is.
以后当有女孩头脑不清 要求和你上床 做就是了
In the future, when a girl asks for some ill-advised sympathy sex, just do it.
等等 你因为昨晚的事生我的气？
Wait, wait, you're, uh, mad at me about last night?
- 我只是不想做错事   - 是吗？
- I was just trying to do the right thing.    - Really?
如果你做的是对的…
If you had done the right thing...
我就不会早上醒来 觉得自己很蠢又笨
...I wouldn't have woken up feeling stupid and embarrassed.
我应该醒来觉得 获得安慰而且满足
I would've woken up feeling comforted and satisfied.
- 好吧   - 少假了
- Well...    - Oh, stop that!
我不敢相信 我只是想要做个好人
I can't believe this! I was just being a good guy.
我用尊重和同情心对待你
I treated you with respect and understanding.
真是迷人
Oh, that is so hot.
我是在保护你
Hey, I was looking out for you.
是吗？你知道吗？我是个大女孩了
Oh, really? Well, you know what? lam a big girl.
我不需要人家来告诉我 什么对我最好
I don't need someone telling me what is best for me.
告诉你 我没有很多性经验 但你是最糟的
I gotta say, I've not had sex a lot of times before. This is the worst ever!
是吗？对我来说 那也是很糟的经验
Oh, oh, really? Really? Well, it wasn't very good for me either.
好吧 你知道吗？
Oh, okay, you know...? Hey, hey, you know what?
以后为了避免这种事
To avoid this little thing in the future...
从今以后 我和你再也不上床
...let's just say, you and me? Never having sex again.
- 什么？ - 没错 上床免谈
- What?    - That's right! Sex is off the table!
我再也不会和你上床
I am never having sex with you again!
葛林医师 有没有觉得好一点？
Dr. Green, are you feeling better?
- 午餐如何？ - 我们很开心
- Hey! How was lunch?    - We had a good time.
另外 我想问你一件事
By the way, I wanted to ask you something.
这对我意义重大 如果宝宝是男孩…
It would really mean a lot to me if the baby was a boy...
如果你能用我父亲的名字为他命名
...that you name him after my father...
吉米尼比利鲍伯
...Jiminy Billy Bob.
- 真的吗？ - 不
- Oh, really?    - No! Ha, ha.
- 你说得没错 很好玩   - 哈哈
- You were right. That was fun.    - Ha-ha-ha.
我要继续去打包了
I'm gonna go finish packing.
- 好   - 哈哈
- Okay.    - Ha, ha.
- 她要去做测试吗？ - 不 她不需要
- So is she gonna take the test?    - No, she doesn't have to.
- 我知道谁是孩子的爸爸了   - 天啊
- I found out who the father is.    - Oh, God.
- 铲子杀手 是吗？ - 不 不是的
- It's Shovely Joe, isn't it'?    - No, it's not.
你怎么知道？
How do you know?
艾瑞卡没有很认真上性教育课
Erica didn't pay attention in sex ed. class...
因为她和蹲苦窑的那家伙做的事
...because the things she did with that prison guy?
那样很难会怀孕
It'd be pretty hard to make a baby that way.
天啊 什么事？我们很少做 还是从没做过的事？
Oh, God, what was it? The thing we hardly ever do, or the thing we never do?
我们从没做过的事
The thing we never do.
铲子杀手
Shovely Joe.
- 乔伊 准备好就开始   - 好的
- Whenever you're ready, Joey.    - Right. Ahem.
- 抱歉 怎么回事？ - 老兄 说说法语吧
- I'm sorry, what's going on?    - Dude, come on, French it up.
乔伊 你会说法语吗？
Joey, do you speak French?
你知道吗？我想试演结束了
You know what? I think this audition is over.
不好意思？
Uh, excuse me?
我是苗吉娜法兰奇
Uh, I am Régine Phalange.
我刚刚经过 听到这位先生说的话…
Uh, I was passing by when I heard this man speaking...
那是法国一个叫做 雅诗兰黛小镇的方言
...the regional dialect of my French town of Estée Lauder.
你真的认为他说的是法语？
You really think this man is speaking French?
（好吧）
（我老实跟你说）
（他是我弟弟）
（他…）
（有点弱智）
（你可以迁就一下他吗？）
讲得好 小兄弟
Good job, little buddy.
你的法语讲得真好
That was some really good French.
但是我们打算请别人来演这个角色
But I think we're gonna go with someone else for the part.
- 好吧 但我的法语很好？ - 非常棒
- Oh, all right, but my French was good?    - It was great.
你看
Oh, ha, ha, see?
- 艾玛已经睡着了   - 那好
- Emma's down for the night.    - Oh, good.
- 我想我该走了   - 好吧
- So, uh, I guess I'm gonna take oh'.    - Okay.
听着 在你走之前…
Hey, listen, uh, just before you go...
我想谢谢你陪我一起去
I just wanna say thank you for coming with me.
别客气
Oh, no problem.
还有 你知道的…
And also, you know, I, uh...
我想了你和我说的话 有关于上床的事
I was thinking about what you said, uh, you know, about the whole sex thing...
走回头路或许不是个好主意
Probably not a great idea to go down that road again.
谢谢你 很高兴你想通了
Thank you. I'm glad you agree.
不过很可惜 我们做得都还不错
It's a shame, though. When we did it, it was pretty good.
是啊
Yeah.
那竟是真的
Yeah, that's true.
你记不记得真的很棒的那一次？
Hey, um, do you remember that one really great time?
- 是啊   - 你记得？
- Oh, yeah!    - You know?
- 情人节   - 你生日的时候
- It was Valentine's Day.    - It was your birthday.
对了
Oh, yeah.
我想那都是过去式了
Well, I guess that's all in the past now.
嗯
Mm-hm.
- 一次都不行   - 一次都不行
- Not even one more time.    - Not even once.
- 不论我们有多想   - 即使我们…
- No matter how much we want it.    - Even if we want it...
- 非常想要   - 我们已经作了决定
-...really bad.    - That's what we decided.
没错
Yeah, ha, ha, that's right.
- 不过有点难 你也知道的   - 是啊
- It's kind of hard, though. You know?    - Yeah.
两个人处得那么好 你知道的…
When two people have a connection, you know, that's...
似乎有点…
Just seems like...
很…
...such a...
浪费
...waste.
我不喜欢浪费
I hate waste.
- 罗斯   - 是的
- Ross?    - Yes?
我想让你知道…
Just so you know...
我们两个
...with us...
永远有得谈
...it's never off the table.
该死 永远有得谈
Damn it, it's never off the table.
- 你真的会跳踢踏舞吗？ - 不会
- Okay, can you really tap-dance?    - No.
从履历表上划掉
It's off the résumé.
- 射箭？ - 不会
- Archery?    - No.
- 骑马   - 会摔得很惨
- Horseback riding?    - Would fall off a lot.
你可以在十秒内 喝完一加仑的牛奶吗？
You can drink a gallon of milk in 10 seconds?
我可以
That I can do.
拜托 你可以在十秒内 喝完一加仑的牛奶？
Come on, you can drink a gallon of milk in 10 seconds?
好 你看着
All right, watch me.
- 好 你准备计时   - 预备 开始
- Okay, you time me, ready?    - Ready, go!
你成功了
You did it!